Karma is coming for us all
Don't Look Back is a horror, thriller, mystery film directed by Jeffrey Reddick.
When a young woman overcoming her traumatic past is among several witnesses who see a man fatally assaulted
and don't intervene, they find themselves targeted by someone, or something, out for revenge.
Caitlin Kramer, played by Kourtney Bell.
Josh Bowman, played by Skyler Hart.
Lucas Helton, played by Will Stout.
Althea Minnis, played by Jaqueline Fleming.
Curt Miley, played by Damon Lipari.
Maria Sanchez, played by Amanda Grace Benitez.
"Don't Look Back in Anger" is a song by English rock band Oasis, released on 19 February 1996 by Creation
Records as the fifth single from their second studio album, (What's the Story) Morning Glory?
"Don't Look Back in Anger" was written by the lead guitarist and chief
songwriter, Noel Gallagher, and produced by Gallagher and Owen Morris.
It was the first Oasis single with lead vocals by Noel, who had previously
only sung lead on B-sides, instead of his brother, Liam.
Noel later sang lead vocals on six other singles.
The single was the second Oasis song to reach number one on the UK singles
chart, and it was certified seven times platinum in the UK.
The music video was directed by Nigel Dick, featuring Oasis
performing at a mansion with a large group of women.
Critically, the song received positive reviews.
It is one of Oasis's signature songs and has been
played at almost every live show.
In later decades, it has been included in retrospective rankings of best songs, and
has been described as an "anthem" by critics in various contexts.
The film explores themes of trauma, death of father, public murder, karma.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.